(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-09T22:52:08.106234",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": false,
"max_retries_exceeded": true,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
可愛くてごめん
[Song: Sorry for Being Cute]
私が私のことを愛して
What's wrong with loving
何が悪いの？ 嫉妬でしょうか？
who I am? Is it jealousy?
痛いだとか 変わってるとか
Calling me cringey or weird...
届きませんね そのリプライ
Your replies don't reach me!
大好きなお洋服
In my favorite outfit,
大好きなお化粧で
with my favorite makeup,
お決まりのハーフツイン巻いて
curling my signature half-twintails,
お出かけしよう 日傘持って
let's head out with a parasol!
ぼっちだって 幸せだもん
Even on my own, I'm so happy!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
生まれちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born this way!
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for playing coy!
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
It catches your eye, right? Sorry!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for putting in all the work!
Chu! 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so precious!
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for having such high girl power!
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまあw
Are you annoyed? Serves you right!
あなたはあなたのことだけどうぞ
You just focus on yourself, please.
私に干渉しないでください
Don't interfere with my life!
類は友を呼ぶと言うけど
They say birds of a feather flock together,
届きませんね その陰口
but your gossip doesn't reach me!
思い出のボク写す
Capturing me in your memories,
お気に入りのリュックで
with my favorite backpack on.
崩せない前髪 くしでといて お出かけしよう
Combing my bangs so they stay perfect, let's go out!
軽い女？ ふざけんな
An easy girl? Don't make me laugh!
重すぎるっつの
I'm way too deep, you know?
Chu！ 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
この時代生きてごめん
Sorry for living in this era!
Chu！ 狙っててごめん
Chu! Sorry for aiming for your heart!
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
You can't help but notice me, right? Sorry!
Chu！ 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
自分磨きしてごめん
Sorry for working on my charm!
Chu！ ぶりっ子でごめん
Chu! Sorry for playing cute!
虜にしちゃってごめん
Sorry for making you fall for me!
ムカついちゃうでしょ？ざまあ
Annoyed yet? Serves you right!
趣味の違い 変わり者と バカにされても
Even if mocked for weird tastes or being eccentric,
負けたくない 怖くもない あんたらごとき
I won't lose, nor am I afraid of people like you.
自分の味方は自分でありたい
I want to be my own biggest supporter,
一番大切にしてあげたい
and cherish myself more than anyone else.
理不尽な我慢はさせたくない
I won't force myself to endure unfairness.
それが私
That's who I am.
Chu！ 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born!
Chu！ あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so calculatedly cute!
人生楽しんでごめん
Sorry for enjoying my life!
Chu！ 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
努力しちゃってごめん
Sorry for putting in the effort!
Chu！ 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so precious!
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for my high feminine charm!
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまあ
Gets on your nerves, right? Serves you right!
現場 現場 現場で絶賛感電中！
On set, on set, electric shocks in progress!
あなたに言い忘れたいこと 悲しいこと あるのかしらね
I wonder if there's anything sad I'd like to forget telling you.
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは ドラマチックが足りてないからよ
Crying at a movie I've never seen is because my life lacks drama.
そんな具にも付かないこと くだらないこと 考えてばかりね
Always thinking about useless, silly things like that.
目が合えば愛もその横顔も 誰かのものになるんでしょう
If our eyes meet, that love and profile will belong to someone else, right?
嘘パッチのファンデーションも全部 今夜のためよ
Even this fake patch of foundation is all for tonight.
なのに一体全体どうしてどうして なぜなぜハテナ
So why, on earth, why, why, why, question mark?
フワッと解けて解けて どこまで行くの あなた一切合切放り出しても
Untangling softly, where are you going, even if you throw everything away?
あぁ冗談じゃない
Ah, you've got to be kidding!
ナイナイわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No way, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
When the time comes, nothing can be done!
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリカするだけ
Vague truths only make me melancholic.
あたしを今更拐って今更興味？ Yes！
Sweeping me away now, interested only now? Yes!
ちゃんちゃらおかしいの ハットばっかりで 祝辞が微塵もしないわ
It's utterly ridiculous, full of surprises without a single word of congratulations.
実体のない感情 放っておいたって 策略なんてあり得ないのに何故
Leaving intangible emotions alone, why, when there's no scheme at play?
あぁもうコリゴリよ 私の勝手な期待感 じっと堪えて取り繕っては 遠回りして
Ah, I've had enough! Holding back my selfish expectations, patching things up, taking the long way around.
年がら年中リップサービス 鈍感かましてはヘキヘキ トンガラガッシャ フィードバックは 涙の目にもニー
Year-round lip service, playing dumb and getting fed up, crashing feedback right in my teary eyes!
大音量のミュージックのせいで あなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
Because of the loud music, I can't hear a single word you're saying.
もしも真っ当なこと言っていたって
Even if you were saying something sensible,
いいえ 廻り出すランデヴーで 全部忘れさせてよ
No, let this spinning rendezvous make me forget everything!
だけど一体全体どうしてどうして なぜなぜハテナ
But why, on earth, why, why, why, question mark?
不安定で消えないままで あなた一向両舌 食い違っても
Unstable, remaining unfaded, even if your double-talking words clash...
あぁ冗談じゃない
Ah, you've got to be kidding!
ナイナイわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No way, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
When the time comes, nothing can be done!
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリカするだけ
Vague truths only make me melancholic.
あだしを今...
Taking me away now...
ホロライブ カウントダウン 2023！ 盛り上がってるー？ いよいよ今年もあと少し！
Hololive Countdown 2023! Are you ready to party? Just a little bit left of this year!
あんなこと こんなこと 色々あったね
Such things, these things, so much has happened,
2023年を最後まで全力で楽しもうね！
Let's enjoy the rest of 2023 with all our might!
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
This is no joke, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たってどうにもなんないぜ
Even when that time comes, nothing can be done.
不甲斐ないわ 感情の波のプール
It's pathetic, this pool of emotional waves,
漂うだけ 私と
just floating along with me.
確かめ合って イエロー・マルチ
Confirming with each other, yellow margin.
イヤイヤイヤ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No, no, no, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たってどうにもなんないぜ
Even when that time comes, nothing can be done.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Vague truths only turn into melancholy.
私をさらっていま Take on me
Take me away, now take on me.
酔いに 酔いが冷めない
Drunk, and I can't sober up,
酔いに 恋が冷めない
drunk, and my love won't cool down.
酔いに 狂い咲くの 慣れて散らして
Drunk, blooming out of season, getting used to it and scattering.
ノーマンタイ 鼻で笑ってみて
Feeling full, laugh it off softly,
Hold me tight トラウマの味も
Hold me tight, even the taste of trauma.
反対 お手お座りで ハイ ぽんしゃ
Fierce opposition, sit and give me your paw, yes, checkmate.
喉の奥が チクンチクン
Deep in my throat, it stings and prickles,
僕は ドクンドクン
my heart goes thump-thump,
鼓動をデコード 解消してみせてよ
decode my heartbeat and break it down for me.
愛好性も 毒殺して
Poisoning affection too,
我を 喪失して
losing myself completely,
このまま 禁中毒になるまで
until I become addicted to this ban,
チューしよう
let me kiss you.
そして ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲロチュー
And then, p-p-puke, p-p-puke, puke kiss!
ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲ・ゲ・ゲロチュー
P-p-puke, p-p-puke kiss!
あいつのゲロ 吐き気に酔いしれた 気持ちが
Drunk on the nausea of that guy's puke, my feelings...
たまらないの ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲロチュー
I can't resist it! P-p-puke, p-p-puke, puke kiss!
ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲ・ゲ・ゲロチュー ゲロ ゲロ
P-p-puke, p-p-puke kiss, puke puke!
お愛に 猛反対
Fiercely opposed to love,
ゲ・ゲ・ゲロチュー
p-p-puke kiss!
ポンチーカン 勝負はいつも
Pong, chow, kan, the match is always...
トンチンカン 僕に言わせりゃ
Irrelevant, if you ask me.
珍紛漢紛 どんな最後は
Total nonsense, what kind of ending...
ロンでしょう
is a win, right?
もう何回 やられればいい
How many more times must I take a blow?
終わんない 忘れられない
It won't end, I can't forget.
終わんない デトキメキ偏愛 予習
It won't end, this throbbing bias love, preparation!
喉の奥が チクンチクン
Deep in my throat, it stings and prickles,
僕は ドクンドクン
my heart goes thump-thump,
心臓ごと 引きずり出してみせてよ
drag out my heart along with it and show me.
気持ちいい 難解 毒性けど
Feels good, complex and toxic, but...
やば 手痛く 臭いけど
oh crap, painful and stinky, but...
死ぬまで 忘れられない
until I die, I won't forget.
チューしよう
Let me kiss you.
イカれた街は ゾンビで溢れる
The crazy city is overflowing with zombies.
君は僕に 恋してる
You're in love with me.
ときめく胸に 繋がるロープを
Pull the rope connected to your throbbing chest!
引きなよ
Pull it!
行くよ ベ・ベ・ベロ ベ・ベ・ベロ ベロチュー
Here we go! L-l-lick, l-l-lick, lick kiss!
ベ・ベ・ベロ ベ・ベ・ベロチュー
L-l-lick, l-l-lick kiss!
マジで狂えるくらいの 毒性
Toxicity that can really make you go insane,
愛しさが 美しいでしょう
this affection... isn't it beautiful?
ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲロチュー
P-p-puke, p-p-puke, puke kiss!
ゲ・ゲ・ゲロ ゲ・ゲ・ゲロチュー
P-p-puke, p-p-puke kiss!
せーの ポンチーカン
One, two, pong, chow, kan!
終わんない ゲ・ゲ・ゲロチュー
It won't end, p-p-puke kiss!
ごらんよ お愛に 猛反対
Look, fiercely opposed to love,
ゲ・ゲ・ゲロチュー
p-p-puke kiss!
君が持ってきた漫画 くれた知らない名前の花
The manga you brought, the flower with an unknown name you gave me...
今日はまだ開かないかな 初めての感情知ってしまった
I wonder if it won't bloom today... I've learned an emotion for the first time.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって ひとりで宇宙を旅して
Tracing the painting placed by the window, traveling through space alone,
それだけでいいはずだったのに
that should have been enough, and yet...
君の手を握ってしまったら
Once I ended up taking your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
to this city that knew no solitude,
もう二度と帰っていけない
I can never return again.
願うことはできないのでしょう
It must be impossible to wish for it, right?
君が手を差し伸ばした
You reached out your hand.
光で影が生まれる
Shadows are born from the light.
歌って聞かせて
Sing to me, let me hear...
この話の続き
...the continuation of this story,
連れていってみたことのない星まで
take me to a star I've never seen before.
誰の手も声も届かない
Where no one's hand or voice can reach,
高くそびえたった塔の上
atop the towering spire.
飛ばす風船 数が
As for the balloons we release...
僕は君に笑ってほしいんだ
I just want you to smile.
満たされない穴は
The hollow void that cannot be filled...
駄生の会話や済ましたポーズで
with superficial talk and composed poses,
これまでは埋めてきたけど
I used to patch it up until now, but...
退屈な日々を抜け出して
If I could escape these dull days,
君と二人で
together with you,
この街を泳げたら
and swim through this city,
それはどれだけ素敵なことでしょう
how wonderful would that be?
出したことのないほどの大きな
With a louder voice than I've ever made,
声でやっと君に伝わる
it finally reaches you.
歪でなく不揃いが 奇跡と調和の取れた
Not warped, but uneven, in harmony with miracles,
世界の端と端を結んで
connecting edge to edge of the world.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって
Tracing the painting decorating the window,
ひとりで宇宙を旅して
traveling through space all alone,
それだけでも不自由ないけど
even if that alone leaves nothing lacking,
僕は選んでみたいの
I want to try choosing,
高鳴る心 謎だらけの空を
with a throbbing heart, through the mystery-filled sky,
安全なルートを今
to rewrite the safe route...
書き換えて
...right now.
君の手を握ってしまったら
If I take hold of your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
to this city that knows no loneliness,
もう二度と帰ってくることはできないのでしょう
we probably can never return again.
いくらでも迷いながら
No matter how lost we get,
光も影も見に行こう
let's go see both the light and the shadows.
歌って聞かせてこの話の続き
Sing to me, let me hear the continuation of this story,
連れていってみたことのない星まで
take me to a star I've never seen before.
世界の端と端を結んで
Connecting edge to edge of the world.
もうすぐ時計は6時
The clock will soon strike six.
もうそこに一番星
The evening star is already there.
影を踏んで
Stepping on shadows,
夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
on the way home, wanting to vanish into the night.
どんなに探してみても
No matter how much I search,
ひとつしかない星
there's only one star.
何億光年
Hundreds of millions of light-years...
離れたところから
From a distant place,
あんなに輝く
shining so brightly.
いいな 君はみんなから愛されて
How nice, you are loved by everyone.
いいな 僕はずっと一人きりさ
How nice, I'm always all alone.
君と集まって星座になれたら 星降る夜 一瞬の願いごと
If I could gather with you and become a constellation, a moment's wish on a starry night,
きらめいて 揺らめいて 震えている シグナル
sparkling, wavering, trembling signal.
君と集まって星座になれたら 空見上げて指をさされるような
If I could gather with you and become a constellation, as if pointing up at the sky,
つないだ線 ほどかないで 僕がどんなに眩しくても
don't untie the connected line, no matter how dazzling I am.
もうすぐ時計は8時 夜空に満天の星
It's almost 8 o'clock, a sky full of stars in the night sky.
何のこれ 離れたところにはもう ないかもしれない
What is this? It might no longer be in a distant place.
月が綺麗で 泣きそうになるのは
The moon is so beautiful, making me feel like crying,
いつもの君から 別れが来るから
because a goodbye comes from the usual you.
君と集まって星座になれたら 彗星みたいに流れるひとりごと
If I could gather with you and become a constellation, a monologue flowing like a comet,
消えていく 残照は 真夜中の プリズム
fading away, the lingering glow is a midnight prism.
君と集まって星座になれたら 切なる願い誰かに届いたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation, if my earnest wish reaches someone,
変われるかな 夜の縁を なぞるような こんな僕でも
can I change? Even someone like me, tracing the edge of night.
はるか彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far, far away, we ended up meeting.
カルマだから 何度出会ってしまおう
Because it's karma, let's meet again and again,
雲の隙間で
in the gaps between the clouds.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
夜広げて 描こう えそらごと
spreading the night, let's draw a pipedream,
暗闇を 照らすような 満月じゃなくても
even if it's not a full moon lighting up the darkness.
だから集まって星座になりたい
So I want to gather and become a constellation,
色とりどりの光 放つような
emitting colorful light.
つないだ線 ほどかないよ
I won't untie the connected line,
君がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling you are.
第ゼロ感
[Title: Dai Zero Kan]
群れをはぐれて 夢を喰い荒らした
Straying from the herd, devouring dreams,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like that would be the last time.
獣の割に素直を 一握り撒いた
For a beast, I scattered a handful of honesty,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like that would be the last time.
不確かな夢叶えるよさ 約束の夜に
The goodness of fulfilling uncertain dreams, on the night of promise,
かすかな風になろうさ 静寂の朝に
let's become a subtle breeze, in the silent morning,
遠い星の証明は
the proof of a distant star is
その腕に約束の飾り
the ornament of promise on that arm,
まだ旅路の最中さ
still in the middle of the journey,
眩惑の園に
in the garden of bewilderment.
かすんで消えた
Vanishing into the haze,
轍の先へ
beyond the tire tracks,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like that would be the end.
手品のような夢を 紡ぎ直せば
If I weave together a dream like magic once more,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like that would be the end.
熱砂を蹴り抗った 約束の前に
Kicking the hot sand, resisting before the promise,
Wo-oh-oh-oh
命綱はないのさ 逆様の夜に
there is no lifeline on this upside-down night,
Wo-oh-oh-oh
まだ旅路の最中さ
still in the middle of the journey,
あの場所に加速するさらに
accelerating even further toward that place.
雨上がりのシャンデリア
A chandelier after the rain,
幻惑の園に
into the garden of dazzling illusion.
Wo-oh-oh-oh
迷走スマッシュ トラブルトラバキ切れみな
Straying smash, trouble, break through it all, everyone!
Wo-oh-oh-oh
迷走スマッシュ トラブルトラバキ切れみな
Straying smash, trouble, break through it all, everyone!
Wo-oh-oh-oh
大丈夫さ
It'll be alright.
Can you hear steel drums sound?
パスコードをペネトレートベースビーバー ゲットトリプルパンタグラフ
Passcode, penetrate, bass beaver, get triple pantograph!
罠だらけのシビアホージェイ バスコダガマビッグバン
Trap-filled severe hole J, Vasco da Gama big bang!
パスコードをペネトレートベースビーバー ゲットトリプルパンタグラフ
Passcode, penetrate, bass beaver, get triple pantograph!
野良犬たちのエクストラパス クワザトビハビ
Stray dogs' extra pass, Kuwazatobihabi!
Wo-oh-oh-oh
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
ランドリー今日はガラ空きでラッキーデイ
Laundromat's wide open today, lucky day!
カタリー油汚れもこれでバイバイ
Bye-bye to all these stubborn grease stains too!
誰だ誰だ頭の中呼びかける声は
Who is it calling out inside my head?
あれが欲しい色が欲しいと歌っている
Singing "I want that, I want this!"
幸せになりたい
I wanna be happy,
楽して生きていたい
I wanna live an easy life,
この手で掴みたい
I wanna hold in my hands
あなたのその胸の中
what's inside your chest.
ハッピーで埋め尽くして レストインピースまで行こうぜ
Fill it with happiness, let's go all the way to "Rest in Peace"!
いつかみた地獄もいいところ
Even that hell I once saw isn't so bad.
愛をばらまいて アイラブユーけなしちゃってくれ
Scatter love around, say "I love you" and trash me!
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
なんか忘れちゃったんだ
I kinda forgot something.
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
よんよんさんで外れる炭酸水
Soda water losing its fizz at 4-4-3
ハングリーこじらせて吐きそうな人生
A life feeling sick from complex hunger
止まない雨はないより先に 傘をくれよ
Before telling me after rain comes sunshine, give me an umbrella
あれが欲しい これが欲しい すべて欲しい たら嬉しい
I want that, I want this, I want it all—that'd make me happy
幸せになりたい
I want to be happy
楽して生きていたい
I want to live an easy life
全部めちゃくちゃにしたい
I want to mess everything up
何もかも消し去りたい
I want to erase everything away
あなたのその胸の中
Inside that chest of yours
ハッピーで埋め尽くして Rest in peace まで行こうぜ
Fill it up with happy, let's go until we rest in peace
良い子だけ迎える天国じゃあ もういらない
A heaven that only welcomes good kids? I don't need it anymore
愛をばらまいて 奪って 笑ってくれ マイハニー
Scatter love, steal it away, and laugh for me, my honey
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
なんか忘れちゃったんだ
I somehow forgot about it
ハッピー ラッキー こんにちは ベイビー
Happy, lucky, hello, baby
良い子でないかい？ そりゃつまらない
Aren't you a good kid? Well, that's boring
ハッピー ラッキー こんにちは ベイビー ソー スウィート
Happy, lucky, hello baby, so sweet
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
なんかすごい感じ
Feels kinda amazing!
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
本当は分かってた いけないことだったって分かってたのに
Truth is, I knew it... even though I knew it was something I shouldn't do.
この手をすり抜ける全部が愛に見えたの
Everything slipping through my hands looked like love.
確かめていた言葉が形になって揺れるだけ
The words I kept confirming take shape and merely sway.
Yeah
弾いて開いてきっとそれだけ つまらないな世界の読み合わせ
Flick it open, surely that's all. How boring, this reading of the world.
あとちょっとね 解りかけてたのに
Just a little more, and I was about to understand...
脳内ハイにして全部忘れちゃえ ズレた間合いと心拍数 合わせ
Get high in the brain and forget it all. Aligning off-beat distance and heart rate...
見つめ合えたら
If our eyes met...
Overdose 君と二人 やるせない日々 幻像
Overdose, just the two of us. Miserable days, illusions.
解る悪い夢を見たい
I get it, I want to see a bad dream.
Overdose 君と二人 甘いハザードに溶かして
Overdose, just the two of us, melting into a sweet hazard.
Music Darling
本当は分かってる いけないことだったって分かっててる 多分
Truth is, I know it... I know it was something I shouldn't do, probably.
時間だけが過ぎていく 徒に満ちていく
Only time passes by, needlessly filling up.
言い訳をする間もなく 裸になってしまうだけ
Without even time to make excuses, I just end up exposed.
Yeah
きっと溜まってくんだずっと 舞ってしまえばいいとふっと
It surely keeps piling up continuously. I suddenly thought, maybe I should just scatter away.
傷んで腐っていくあの甘い果実のように僕ら壊れていく
Like that sweet fruit rotting away, we are breaking down.
だから脳内ハイにして全部忘れちゃえ 浅はかな僕ら隣り合わせ
So get high in the brain and forget it all. Shallow as we are, side by side...
見つめ合えたら
If our eyes met...
Overdose 君と二人 分かり合いたいのに お互い
Overdose, just the two of us. Even though we both want to understand each other,
今のままの二人 嘘が嫌い
being who we are right now, we hate lies.
Overdose 君と二人 分かり合いたいのに Two step for me darling
Overdose, just the two of us. Even though I want to understand you, two step for me, darling.
Ah ah ah ah yeah
Overdose 君と二人 やるせない日々 幻像
Overdose, just the two of us. Miserable days, illusions.
解る悪い夢を見たい
I get it, I want to see a bad dream.
Overdose 君と二人 甘いハザードに溶かして
Overdose, just the two of us, melting into a sweet hazard.
Music Darling
Overdose 君と二人 分からない
Overdose, just the two of us, I don't know...
煙にまくワンルーム
In a smoke-filled one-room apartment,
嘘でもいいから
even if it's a lie, it's fine,
今夜は君と二人
tonight, just the two of us.
甘いハザード
A sweet hazard.
Don't stop the music, darling
凍りついた心には太陽を
A sun for a frozen heart,
そして僕が君にとってそのポジションを
and for me to hold that position for you...
そんな大層な傲慢な思い込みを抱かせてたんだよ
I made you hold onto such grand, arrogant assumptions.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
笑ってやって
Go ahead and laugh at me.
火傷しそうなほどのポジティブの冷たさと残酷さに気付いたんだよ
I realized the coldness and cruelty of a positivity so intense it could burn.
きっと君に渡したいものは
Surely what I want to give you
もっとひんやり熱いもの
is something even cooler and hotter.
綺麗事じゃないけど 綺麗で揺るぎないもの
It's not just lip service, but something beautiful and unwavering,
上べよりも胸の奥の奥を温めるもの
something that warms deep within your chest rather than the surface.
理想だけはあるけど 心のどこ探しても まるで見つからないんだよ
I have my ideals, but no matter where I search in my heart, I can't find it at all.
伝えたい 伝わらない そこに条理が今
I want to convey, but it doesn't get across, and right there lies logic,
キツく縛りつけんだよ
tightly binding us down now.
臆病な僕の
Of my cowardly self,
この一挙手一投足の
in every single move of mine...
言葉はまるで雪の結晶
Words are just like snowflakes.
君にプレゼントしたくても
Even if I want to give them to you as a gift,
夢中になればなるほど
the more engrossed I get,
形は崩れ落ちて溶けていって 消えてしまうけど
their shape breaks down, melts away, and disappears, but...
でも僕が選ぶ言葉が そこに託された思いが
But the words I choose, the feelings entrusted in them...
君の胸を震わすのを
Making your heart vibrate...
諦められない 愛してるよりも愛が届くまで
I can't give up until love reaches you, more than saying "I love you."
もう少しだけ待ってて
Please wait just a little longer.
薄着でただそばに立ってても 不必要に汗をかいてしまう僕なんかは
Even standing beside you lightly dressed, someone like me who sweats unnecessarily
どうしたって生ぬるくて君を痛め続けてしまうのだろう
will probably remain lukewarm and keep hurting you no matter what.
手のひらが熱いほど 心は冷たいんでしょう?
The hotter the palms, the colder the heart, right?
冗談でもそんな残酷なこと言わないでよ
Don't say such cruel things, even as a joke.
別に言えない訳の全人生を賭けても ちゃんと覆させてよ
Even if I stake my entire life of unsaid reasons, let me properly overturn it.
救いたい 救われたい このイコールが今
I want to save, I want to be saved, this equation now
優しく剥がしていくんだよ
is gently peeling away.
硬い理論武装
Hard theoretical armor,
プライドの過剰包装
over-packaging of pride.
正しさよりも優しさが欲しい
I want kindness more than correctness,
そしてそれを受け取れるのは
and the one who can receive it...
イルミネーションみたいな
Is not an unspecified crowd
不特定多数じゃなくてただ一人 君であってほしい
lit up like Christmas lights, but just one person—I want it to be you.
かけた言葉割れ 裂けたヒビを直そうとして
Trying to fix the cracks and splits from spoken words,
足しすぎた不自然さで
with unnaturalness from adding too much,
惹かれてしまっていたんだ
I ended up being drawn to it.
そんな失敗作を重ねて
Accruing such failures,
見つけるんだいつか
I'll find it someday...
最高の一行を
The single best line.
言葉はまるで雪の結晶 君にプレゼントしたくても
Words are like snowflakes; even if I want to give them to you as a gift,
時間が経ってしまえばたいてい 記憶からこぼれ落ちて溶けていって 消えてしまっても
even if time passes and they mostly spill from memory, melt away, and disappear...
絶えず僕らのストーリーに
Incessantly, in our story,
添えられた字幕のように
like subtitles appended to it,
思い返した時に
when looking back,
ふいに目をやる時に
when suddenly turning our eyes to it,
君の胸を震わすものを 探し続けたい
I want to keep searching for what makes your heart vibrate.
愛が届くまで
Until my love reaches you
もう少しだけ待ってて
Wait for me just a little longer
言葉など何も欲しくないほど
So much that I don't need any words
悲しみに凍りつく夜でも
Even on nights frozen in sadness
勝手に君のそばで
Selfishly by your side
あれこれと考えてる
Thinking about this and that
雪が溶けても残ってる
Still remaining even after the snow melts
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know, you want it, right?
艶やかな この唇
These glossy lips
柔らかい とこ立ち引き寄せる
Pulling you close to my soft parts
吐息の無法地に甘い蜜
Sweet nectar in the lawless zone of my breath
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know, you want it, right?
見透かすの この身体
You see right through this body
朝は無知 街一人歩けば
Naive in the morning, walking alone in the city
似たような視線が絡みつくね
Similar gazes entangle around me, don't they?
何を期待してるの
What are you expecting?
その気じゃなくて 今すぐがいいの
Not just getting into the mood, I want it right now
大人の恋に焦がれて
Longing for an adult love
見た目よりも残るあどけない
More innocent than I look
心だけが先走る
Only my heart rushes ahead
追いつかないまま オトナブルー
Unable to catch up, Adult Blue
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know, you want it, right?
刺激する 私のすべて
Stimulating all of me
散った日 遠くまで魅了する
Captivating far away even after the petals fall
いつかは花になる アマリリス
Someday becoming a flower, Amaryllis
形だけの言葉じゃなくて
Not just superficial words
心で繋がりたくて
Wanting to connect from the heart
ありきたりなメイクじゃ隠せない
Ordinary makeup can't hide it
憧れたけど 夢を見る
I longed for it, but I still dream
あなたの前でまた オトナブルー
In front of you, once again, Adult Blue
その気じゃなくて 今すぐがいいの
Not just getting into the mood, I want it right now
大人の恋に焦がれて
Longing for an adult love
見た目よりも残るあどけない
More innocent than I look
気持ちだけが空回り
Only my feelings spin in circles
私を見つけて
Find me
形だけの言葉じゃなくて
Not just superficial words
心で繋がりたくて
Wanting to connect from the heart
ありきたりなメイクじゃ隠せない
Ordinary makeup can't hide it
憧れたけど 夢を見る
I longed for it, but I still dream
まだ見ぬ恋心を
A love I have yet to know
追いかけて 追いかけて...
Chasing after, chasing after...
ブルー
Blue
外出た瞬間 終わったわ
The moment I stepped outside, it was over
天気はいいのに 進めない
The weather is fine, but I can't move forward
風強すぎて お散歩にならない
The wind is too strong, it's impossible to take a walk
定期的にオールバック
Periodically pushed back into an all-back hairstyle
地下に潜りたいな
I want to retreat underground
思い付きました
I've come up with an idea:
コンセント減なくなれば
If we ran out of power outlets,
あったかいのに
even though it's warm...
ずっと座りたいな
I want to sit down the whole time.
って思い付きました
...is what came to mind.
いいないいな 外出たら
How nice, how nice, when I stepped outside...
ハト ハト ハト ハト 大乱闘
Pigeons, pigeons, pigeons, pigeons in a free-for-all!
外出た瞬間 終わったわ
The moment I stepped outside, I was done for.
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather is clear, but I can't move forward.
風強すぎてお亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I'm dead.
定期 定期的にオールバック
Periodically slicked back.
今年もみんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone for this year!
来年のホロライブも勢いは
Next year, Hololive's momentum...
止まらねぇー！
...won't stop!
外出た瞬間 終わったわ
The moment I stepped outside, I was done for.
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather is clear, but I can't move forward.
風強すぎてお亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I'm dead.
定期 定期的にオールバック
Periodically slicked back.
外出た瞬間 終わったわ
The moment I stepped outside, I was done for.
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather is clear, but I can't move forward.
風強すぎてお亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I'm dead.
定期 定期的にオールバック
Periodically slicked back.
髪の毛強風オールバック
Hair completely slicked back by strong wind!
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
Taking the media by storm with an invincible smile,
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
I want to know her mysterious secrets.
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even her clumsy side is part of her domain.
完璧で嘘つきな君は
Perfect, yet a liar,
天才的なアイドル様
you are a genius idol.
今日何食べた？ 好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
If you're going out to play, where do you go?
何も食べてない それは内緒
"I haven't eaten anything"—that's a secret.
何を聞かれても のらりくらり
No matter what you ask, dodging every question smoothly.
そう淡々と だけど爛々と
So coolly, yet brightly shining,
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
a secret seemingly visible yet hidden tastes like honey.
あれもないないない
That isn't there, no, no, no.
これもないないない
This isn't there, no, no, no.
好きなタイプは？ 相手は？ さあ答えて
What's your type? Who is it? Come on, answer me!
誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ
"I don't really know what it's like to love someone."
嘘か本当か知り得ない
Is it a lie or the truth? There's no way to know.
そんな言葉にまた一人落ちる
With words like that, another one falls for her.
また好きにさせる
Making them fall in love with her again.
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone has their eyes captivated,
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
you are the perfect, ultimate idol.
金輪際現れない
Never to appear again,
一番星の生まれ変わり
the reincarnation of the brightest star.
その笑顔で「愛してる」で
With that smile, with that "I love you",
誰も彼も虜にしていく
captivating each and every person.
その瞳が その言葉が
Those eyes, those words,
嘘でもそれは完全なアイ
even if fake, it's a perfect love.
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yeah, yeah, that girl is special.
我々はハナからおまけです
We're just sidekicks from the start.
お星様の引き立て役Bです
We're just background filler B for the star.
すべてがあの子のおかげなわけない
There's no way everything is thanks to her...
しゃらくさい 妬み嫉妬なんてないわけがない
How annoying! How could there not be envy and jealousy?
これはネタじゃない からこそ許せない
This isn't a joke! That's why I can't forgive it!
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない 自分を許せない
If you're not perfect, I can't forgive you! I can't forgive myself!
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't accept anyone other than you, who is stronger than anyone!
誰もが信じ崇めてる
Everyone believes in and worships her,
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
truly the strongest, invincible idol.
弱点なんて見当たらない
No flaws to be found anywhere,
一番星を宿している
harboring the brightest star within.
弱いところなんて見せちゃダメダメ
You must never, ever show any weakness.
知りたくないところは見せずに
Keep what people don't want to see hidden.
唯一無二じゃなくちゃ イヤイヤ
You must be one of a kind, no, no!
それこそ本物の愛
That is what true love is!
得意の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Exciting the media with her signature smile,
隠し通すこの秘密だけは
keeping this secret completely hidden,
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア
building a career on the lie of "I love you."
これこそ私なりの愛だ
This is love in my own way.
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Even the flowing sweat is beautiful aqua,
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
eyelids concealing rubies.
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
Singing, dancing, and twirling, I am Maria.
そう嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, lies are an extraordinary love!
誰かに愛されたことも
Never having been loved by anyone,
誰かのこと愛したこともない
and never having loved anyone before,
そんな私の嘘がいつか本当になること
I believe that my lies will one day become true.
信じてる
I believe in it.
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
Someday I'll surely get everything.
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
Yes, I am a greedy idol.
等身大でみんなのことちゃんと愛したいから
Because I want to love everyone properly, as my true self.
今日も嘘をつくの この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
I tell lies again today, praying for the day when these words will come true.
Error processing subtitles for this segment.
こんばんはー！
Good evening!
にょにょにょにょ！
Nyonyonyonyo!
あいつは魔法の過剰摂取で沸点がパ～になったんや
She overdosed on magic and completely lost her marbles!
お前も喰らえー！
Take this too!
こぼも！こぼも！
Kobo too! Kobo too!
なにっ？この…ガキには早いんだよなー
What? This is... way too early for kids!
ガキじゃない！ガキって言った方がガキなんです！
Not a kid! The one calling someone a kid is the kid!
あ、危険！
Ah, watch out!
えー、もうつまんない。
Ehh, so boring.
次の楽屋行こう。
Let's go to the next dressing room.
お邪魔～！ / 赤ん坊が寝てる最中でしょうが！
Pardon me~! / The baby is trying to sleep!
赤ちゃんじゃないのに起きちまったのろー
I'm not a baby, but you woke me up...
私たちも寝ましょうか、お父さん。
Shall we go to sleep too, Father?
誰がお父さんだ！
Who's "Father"?!
こぼも寝る！こぼも！
Kobo wants to sleep too! Kobo too!
しょうがないなー、父様が寝かしつけてあげよう。
Can't be helped then, Father will tuck you in.
僕もご一緒していいかな？
May I join you as well?
母さん！あの男は誰だー！？
Mother! Who is that man?!
違うのよ！違うのよ！
It's not what you think! It's not what you think!
赤ん坊の芝居にも疲れちまったよ...
I'm tired of playing the baby...
じゃあママがマイク代わるわね。
Then Mama will take the mic now.
次の楽屋はこちらでーす。
The next dressing room is this way!
こんばんはー！
Good evening!
これ先輩が回りすぎて止まりません！
These seniors are spinning so fast they won't stop!
止まれー！
Stop!
と、とりあえずインタビューを... マイクがー！
A-Anyway, let's do the interview... My mic!
この状況でインタビューは無理です！
An interview is impossible in this situation!
チョコ先生も手伝って！ / えー！
Choco-sensei, help us too! / Ehhh?!
じゃ、勝手に隣行っちゃおー！
Well then, I'll just head next door on my own~!
あやめ様ー！手伝ってー！あやめ様ー！
Ayame-sama! Help us! Ayame-sama!
可愛くなくてごめん いつも暗くて...
Sorry for not being cute, for always being gloomy...
可愛くなくてごめん 寒くて...
Sorry for not being cute, for being cold...
可愛くなくてごめん 不機嫌で...
Sorry for not being cute, for being moody...
オタ芸の棒がこんなところに！
Otagei glowsticks in a place like this!
まだまだこれからステージあるのに！やめてくださいそのテンション！
We still have stages ahead of us! Please stop that mood!
あれ？ぺこら先輩は反応ないでござるか？
Huh? Pekora-senpai has no reaction?
可愛くてごめん
Sorry for being cute~
このウサギ自己肯定感高ッ！
This rabbit has crazy high self-esteem!
こらこら、みんな可愛いよ！それじゃあ...
Now now, everyone is cute! Well then...
3、2、1...
3, 2, 1...
あ、そんなこんなで...
Ah, after all that...
あと数十秒で年越しだ！
There's only a few dozen seconds left until the New Year!
いや～、長いようで短かったですね～
Man, it felt long yet short, didn't it?
来年ももっともっともっと！
Next year, more and more and more!
みんなと一緒に！
Together with everyone!
ほら！みんな屋上に集まれ～！
Look! Everyone, gather on the rooftop!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0!
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
Everything is gonna be alrightな感じを今 噂のFeeling tuned
Feeling like everything is gonna be alright, right now with that rumored Feeling tuned
Are you ready? コンコンコン Yes! こんなキツネに化かされて
Are you ready? Kon kon kon, Yes! Bewitched by a fox like this
Knock, knock, knock! 心を開けて
Knock, knock, knock! Open up your heart
Oo-yeah-yeah! Everything is gonna be alrightな感じを今 噂のFeeling tuned
Oo-yeah-yeah! Feeling like everything is gonna be alright, right now with that rumored Feeling tuned
Woah-oh-oh! コンコンコン 魔法をかけて Ooh baby, 明くる日まで Feeling tuned!
Woah-oh-oh! Kon kon kon, cast a spell, Ooh baby, Feeling tuned until tomorrow comes!
静寂に響いてよ My howling
Echo through the silence, my howling
瞬きは弧を描き 月へ響く
The twinkling traces an arc, echoing to the moon
爪弾く道 金瞳の群れ 共に嘆く夜
A path plucked out, a pack of golden eyes, a night grieving together
感涙 伝播する想いは 心強くする
Tears of emotion, propagating feelings make my heart grow strong
隣に君がいるから 私は迷わない
Because you are by my side, I will not stray
光射す道へ
Towards the path where light shines
Listen to My howling...
狼が止まることはない
A wolf will never stop
闇に紛れ 甘い処に届いた
Creeping into the darkness, reaching a sweet place,
畳んだ翼 繋いでは解いた
Folded wings, binding and unbinding them,
仮の姿 化けて人に扮して
Disguised in a temporary form as a human,
呼吸が痛むのね
Breathing feels painful, doesn't it?
DING DONG DING DONG 聞かせて
DING DONG DING DONG, let me hear it,
届けて
deliver it.
DING DONG DING DONG 鳴らしてよ
DING DONG DING DONG, ring it out!
凛と 闇が 咲いた
Dignified, darkness bloomed.
止むのが先か
Will it stop first?
借り返しやしないわ
I won't return the favor,
慰めもしないわ
nor will I offer comfort.
私のものね
It belongs to me, right?
飽きたの リスタート
I got bored, restart!
ポポポポポポポポ！ ネネネネネネネネ！ ネ！
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po! Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne! Ne!
ポポポ ネネネネネネネネ！
Po-po-po ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne!
ポポポポポポポポ！ ネネネネネネネネ！ ネ！ ポポポポポポポポ！ ネネネネネネネネ！
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po! Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne! Ne! Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po! Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne!
Baby, hold the line. Are you living free?
Let's forget everything and have some fun!
3, 2, 1, JUMP!
君を ALL THAT SWEET, SWEET, SWEET, SWEET TIME!
Taking you to all that sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet time!
BABY 1, 2, 3 絶好調に TOUCHING 肯定感!
Baby 1, 2, 3, touching self-esteem in top condition!
ギリギリ SO LOUD! ギリギリ SO HIGH! GET HIGH!
Barely SO LOUD! Barely SO HIGH! GET HIGH!
KEEP ON GIVING IT ALL! JUST SHOW THEM YOUR BEST TRY!
ほら全員集合! もう息切れそう!
Hey, everyone gather round! I'm almost out of breath!
WHAT'S YOU DOING RIGHT NOW? さあ振り切れ!
WHAT'S YOU DOING RIGHT NOW? Come on, break free!
3, 2, 1, LET'S GO!
CLAP YOUR HANDS, MOVE IT, BABY, DANCE, YEAH!
CLAP YOUR HANDS, MOVE IT, BABY, DON'T MISS IT!
CLAP YOUR HANDS, MOVE IT, BABY, TOUCH IT!
DANCE WITH ME, BABY!
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE, LOVE, LOVE!
YEAH!
Love, hate, all the same. If you know, play the game.
I'm locked up, but I know I can wipe the feeling on the wall.
Let me, you decide if you want me to stop the line.
Love is just a game, I can play to do the same, oh.
Do you, do you say you do feel insane?
Touch me like a frame, I know I'll never be the same, oh.
Oh yeah, oh yeah. Really I'm just okay.
Love is just a game, love, hate, I can play.
Do you, do you say you do feel insane?
Oh, oh, oh, really I'm just okay.
さあ ダーダダダダダ 封印された部位の名前を
Come on, da-da-da-da-da, the names of the sealed parts...
言えない 言えない こんな強い言葉は
I can't say them, can't say them, such strong words,
少しだけ静かにしてほしいのね
I want you to be quiet for just a little bit.
私たち対立構造？ 今更見たい意味高かったはずなのに
Are we in a confrontation? Even though it was supposed to have high meaning that we wanted to see now...
世界点点転覆 いやいやいや 見過ごすその日まで
World dot-dot-dot overturning, no no no, until the day we overlook it,
とうとう制限 言言言 これの言葉よ よよよ
Finally restriction, word-word-word, these words, yo-yo-yo-yo,
完全転覆 さあさあさあ あなたのおまじない中
Complete overturning, come on come on come on, in the middle of your spell,
風つくるわ パンテオン
Creating wind, Pantheon.
世界点点転覆 いやいやいや 果てすその日まで
World dot-dot-dot overturning, no no no, until that day comes to an end,
例例例覆 いやいやいや あなたの森を よよよ
Ex-ex-ex-overturning, no no no, your forest, yo-yo-yo-yo,
完全点点転覆 さあさあさあ 暗黒の地まで
Complete dot-dot-dot overturning, come on come on come on, to the land of darkness,
高括ったら ヴィンテージのワイン わけましょう
If we underestimate it, let's share the vintage wine.
フセ レヴィア プリ セイ ベルキア デヴィ
Fuse... Levia... Puri... Sei... Belkia... Devi...
雨が降る夜 涙に映った星
On a rainy night, stars reflected in tears,
光った月が...
the glowing moon...
消えてゆく
Fading away...
指先が揺らゆらか
My fingertips sway gently.
その動きが
That movement,
止まった時計の
like a spider stepping onto
針に踏み込んだ
the hands of a stopped clock,
蜘蛛が描いた糸が...
the thread it spun...
そよぐ風に
In the gentle breeze,
その笑顔を知っているよ
I know that smile.
私 ちゃんとフツーと真面目の境界を見せつけたい
I wanna show the exact line between normal and serious.
背徳的なジョークと
With an immoral joke...
戻したい 戻したい 持ちたい 持ちたいなら
If you wanna go back, wanna go back, wanna have it, wanna have it...
人生リセットボタン ポチー
Life reset button, click!
人生リセットのダミー
A dummy of a life reset!
人生リセットボタン ポチー
Life reset button, click!
まず敷き詰めるコンクリート
First, pave down the concrete.
空が落とす一切から Wait time
Waiting out whatever drops from the sky.
縄張りだから
Because this is my turf,
ムチムチキリンやひよっこを飛ばす
sending buff giraffes and novices flying!
絶頂の毎夜
The peak of every night,
ねんねんころね
Nen-nen-korone.
Oh yeah!
ギラギラWammy ボスはカピョンヘン
Glittering Whammy, the boss is Capy-hen!
Oh yeah!
ツルンのパリー
Smooth parry!
おりこうに待ってる
Waiting obediently,
ワンワンワン Loud-da-da-da あっさりのままさ
Woof woof woof, Loud-da-da-da, keeping it simple.
ワンワンワン Da-da-da
Woof woof woof, Da-da-da!
振るうなこの生き様
Brandishing this way of life,
スキャンダルは離さない
won't let go of scandal.
ワンチャンスで輝く
Shining in a single chance,
絶対的レギュラーの
the absolute regular!
オーケー オーケー 僕が君の
Okay, okay, I'll become
神様になってあげる
a god for you!
あーね！ いいじゃん！ うんうん 偉い！ おー 完璧！
Ah, I see! Sounds good! Yeah yeah, good job! Oh, perfect!
今日も疲れた？
Tired again today?
グッド！ でっこう！ でっこう！ でっこう！
Good! Great! Great! Great!
多少は自信持って？
Have a little confidence!
これで！ 素晴らしい世界！
With this, a wonderful world!
近くにいるよ 大好き 超好き つまり好き
I'm right near you! Love you, super love you, in short, love you!
生きてるだけでなんとかなるよ
Just staying alive makes everything work out!
にっこり ぬくぬく 超可愛い
Smiling, cozy, super cute!
君もレッツ「神様」！
You too, let's "God"!
いいじゃん！ いいじゃん！ すごいじゃん！ すごい！
Sounds good! Sounds good! That's awesome! Amazing!
いいじゃん！ いいじゃん！ 偉いじゃん！ 偉い！
Sounds good! Sounds good! Good job! Great!
そうです！ そうです！ もっと僕の
That's right! That's right! Come closer to me,
そばにおいでよ 全肯定！
total affirmation!
いいじゃん！ いいじゃん！ すごいじゃん！ すごい！
Sounds good! Sounds good! That's awesome! Amazing!
いいじゃん！ いいじゃん！ 偉いじゃん！ 偉い！
Sounds good! Sounds good! Good job! Great!
オーケー オーケー 僕が君の
Okay, okay, I'll become
お神様になってあげる
a dear god for you!
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
Guided by the voices calling out to each other!
パレ パレ パレ 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade, off to search!
スタートは何度だって
We can start over as many times as it takes!
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
暗がりを満たすのは
The one filling the darkness...
君だ
is you!
僕だ
It's me!
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
悔しさも愛おしさも連れておいで
Bring along both your regrets and affection!
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光り
A modest prayer shines bright,
終わりのない行き先
toward an endless destination,
君と飛び込んでゆく
leaping in together with you!
素敵なスタートさ
What a wonderful start!
ここから これから
From here, from now on!
アワープラネット パレ パレ
Our Planet Parade Parade!
ハッピーしねえ？ そろそろ考えなくっちゃ
Wouldn't it be happy? We should start thinking about it soon.
みんながちょっとうるさいし まずは作戦会議
Everyone's getting a bit noisy, so first, a strategy meeting!
あっけない 今から始まるラブストーリーとか
Anticlimactic, like a love story about to start right now?
そんなんじゃないし 本命だし
It's not like that, you're my favorite after all.
今日が本番だって
Today's the big day!
ウソウソ 大事なのはここから1ヶ月で知りたいな
Just kidding! What matters is wanting to get to know each other over the next month.
大人になったって ドキドキしてたいもんだって 両思いの先は薔薇色
Even as adults, we still want our hearts to race. Beyond mutual love lies a rosy world!
うんっと
So much!
甘い 甘い 甘い 甘い 甘いの好き 好き 好き 好き 好きって言う私が選んだ君は とびきりのスウィート
"I love, love, love, love, love super sweet things!" That's what I say, and the one I chose is the ultimate sweet!
甘い 甘い 甘い 甘い 1年で一番の贅沢でもしちゃいましょうよ
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet! Let's indulge in the biggest treat of the year!
ちょッ ちょッ ちょッとチョコっとは 予算とカロリーとかオーバーでもね あー
Ju-ju-just a little bit of chocolate, even if it goes over budget and calories, ahh!
ちょッ ちょッ ちょッとチョコレート 私の恋とかにご褒美をあげたい
Ju-ju-just a bit of chocolate, I want to reward my love!
もう今日だって大体は決めました
I've pretty much decided today already.
グチグチ言って送って何が分かったの？
What did you learn by sending all those complaints?
そう でもやっぱみんなソワソワしちゃうな それはそうだけどね
Even so, everyone gets so restless. That's understandable though.
余裕見せたらそれも変かな
Would it be weird if I played it cool?
ねえ 呼び出しなんて何々？
Hey, why are you calling me out?
今日のところは分かれて楽しみたかったのにな
I just wanted to split up and enjoy today, though.
でもあれ？私が欲しかった可愛いやつじゃない？
Wait, isn't that the cute thing I wanted?
気になる これからどうするの？
I'm curious, what are you going to do now?
で、もっと
And even more!
甘い 甘い 甘い 甘い 甘いの好き 好き 好き 好き 好き そんな私にあなたがくれた とびきりのサプライズ
I love, love, love, love, love super sweet things! That's who I am, and you gave me the ultimate surprise!
ヤバい ヤバい ヤバい ヤバい そんなこと 想像もしてなかったの 眠れないね
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, I didn't even imagine that! I can't sleep now!
1ヶ月も悩むなんて そんなの無理じゃない？
Worrying for a whole month? Isn't that just impossible?
私毎日が本命 全力 そういうのが好きでごめん
For me, every day is the real deal, full power! Sorry that I'm just like this!
うんっと
So much!
甘い 甘い 甘い 甘い 甘いの好き 好き 好き 好き 好きって言う私を選んだ君は とびきりのスウィート
"I love, love, love, love, love super sweet things!" You chose the me who says that, you're the ultimate sweet!
甘い 甘い 甘い 甘い 1年で一番の贅沢でもしちゃいましょう
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet! Let's indulge in the biggest treat of the year!
うんっと
So much!
甘い 甘い 甘い 甘い 甘いの好き 好き 好き 好き 好きって言う私が選んだ君は とびきりのスウィート
"I love, love, love, love, love super sweet things!" That's what I say, and the one I chose is the ultimate sweet!
甘い 甘い 甘い 甘い 1年で一番の贅沢でもしちゃいましょうよ
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet! Let's indulge in the biggest treat of the year!
ちょッ ちょッ ちょッとチョコっとは 予算とカロリーとかオーバーでもね あー
Ju-ju-just a little bit of chocolate, even if it goes over budget and calories, ahh!
ちょッ ちょッ ちょッとチョコレート 私の恋とかにご褒美をあげたい
Ju-ju-just a bit of chocolate, I want to reward my love!
私の今日からにご褒美をあげたい
I want to reward myself starting today!
みんなできたー？
Did everyone make it?
できたー！
We did!
まだあるよ！
There's still more!
まだあるからね！
There's still more to come!
はい！次は！
Alright! Next up...
チームBで！
...is Team B!
ショウタイムだ！
It's showtime!
宙に落ちていくシャンデリア
A chandelier falling into the air
痛みに火を点すネオンライト
Neon lights igniting the pain
4 5 6 鳴らせ Clap
4, 5, 6, make some noise, clap!
スポットライトを浴びて
Basking in the spotlight
さあ行こうか劇場へ
Come, shall we head to the theater?
開演さ It's show time
The curtain rises, it's showtime
つらっと踊るステップ本能
Dancing naturally, stepping on instinct
見渡す視線は向こうのほう
Gaze looking far out into the distance
急転直下 心臓はチックアンドタックほら
A sudden plunge, the heart goes tick and tack, look
9 8 Action
7 8 あがっていく
7, 8, climbing higher
悩んで煽っていく
Fretting, hyping it up
緊張感を解き放つ頃
Just when releasing the tension
一瞬へ It's show time
Into this moment, it's showtime
AMP UP 僕の感性を
Amp up my sensibility
AMP UP 更新中
Amp up, updating
AMP UP 君の感性に
Amp up, to your sensibility
AMP UP 挑戦中
Amp up, challenging
AMP UP 研ぎ澄ましていく
Amp up, sharpening it all
AMP UP この一瞬
Amp up, this single moment
AMP UP 君の感情の
Amp up, of your emotions
支配者さ Show Time
I'm the ruler, showtime
It's show time
It's showtime
Crazy にしちゃって
Make them go crazy
It's show time
It's showtime
自由に
Freely
夢みたいな時間を
A dreamlike time
溜まった声を聞かせて頂戴な
Let me hear those bottled-up voices
湧きあがる感情の狂乱が
The frenzy of surging emotions
君をも飲み込んでさ
Swallows you up too
僕をも飲み込んでさ
Swallows me up too
善も悪も愛も歓喜も
Good and evil, love and delight
僕の思い通り
Just as I desire
二度と孤独になんてなれないよ
You can never be lonely again
More Crazy 僕の合図で
More crazy, at my signal
More Crazy 君は依存症
More crazy, you're addicted
It's show time
It's showtime
一つになって
Becoming as one
会場に響くこの歓声
This cheer echoing through the venue
毎秒描いていく世界で
In a world drawn second by second
壇上から揺さぶる感性
Shaking sensibilities from the stage
泣きそうなほどに重なって
Overlapping so deeply it brings tears
歓喜のアリアで編んでいくコード
Chords woven with an aria of joy
今僕らの思いを Random
Now, sending our feelings out at random
君の鼓動を誘発する Show Time
Triggering your heartbeat, showtime
そう僕らを繋ぐよ Show Time
Yes, connecting us, showtime
It's show time
It's showtime
Crazy にしちゃって
Make them go crazy
It's show time
It's showtime
自由に
Freely
夢みたいな時間を
A dreamlike time
It's show time
It's showtime
More Crazy
It's show time
It's showtime
皆さん！楽しめましたかー？
Everyone! Did you enjoy yourselves?
ちょっとね、みんな疲れてると思うけど
I know everyone's a bit tired, but...
あと1曲あります！
We have one last song!
最後の曲はホロライブプロダクション全員で MY舞☆TONIGHT！
For the final song, all of Hololive Production presents MY MAI TONIGHT!
踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance!
熱くなるため
In order to burn with passion,
人は生まれたはずさ
people were surely born!
今小さく燃えてる まだ小さな篝火が
The small bonfire that burns softly now,
ひとつになれば 奇跡が生まれ
if united as one, will create a miracle!
この世界はいつも 諦めない心に
In this world, to a heart that never gives up,
答えじゃなく 道を探す
not an answer, but a clue to find the path...
手がかりをくれるから
...will be given to you!
最後まで強気で行こう！
Let's stay confident until the very end!
踊れ 踊れ 熱くなるため
Dance, dance! To get fired up,
人は生まれてきたの
people were born into this world!
踊れ 踊れ きっとそうだよ
Dance, dance! I'm sure that's how it is,
だから 夢見て踊ろう
so let's dream and dance!
MY舞☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
MY Dance☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
最高の
Let's make today
MY舞☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
MY Dance☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
今日にしよう
the absolute best!
いつか広がるだろう
Someday it will spread out,
ほら大きくひろがれ
look, spread far and wide!
がんばる力が
The power of trying our best
奇跡を呼んでいる
is calling forth a miracle.
この世界の中で 輝きたい心が
When hearts that wish to shine in this world
集まるとき
gather together,
新しいこと
a new idea strikes
思いつき走り出す
and we start running forward!
足元が見えないけど
Even if we can't see where we step,
羽みたいに手を伸ばして
reach out our arms like wings!
踊れ 踊れ 憧れたのは
Dance, dance! What we longed for
ずっと 瞬く光
was always the twinkling light.
踊れ 踊れ きっといつかは
Dance, dance! Let's dance, believing
叶うはずだと踊ろう
it will surely come true someday!
MY舞☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
MY Dance☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
明日へと
Let me connect this
MY舞☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
MY Dance☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
つなげよう
to tomorrow!
夢の声に導かれて
Guided by the voice of our dreams,
道がまた開けたよ
the path has opened up again!
最後まで強気で行こう
Let's stay confident until the very end!
踊れ 踊れ 熱くなるため
Dance, dance! To get fired up,
人は生まれてきたの
people were born into this world!
踊れ 踊れ きっとそうだよ
Dance, dance! I'm sure that's how it is,
だから 夢見て踊ろう
so let's dream and dance!
MY舞☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
MY Dance☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
最高の
Let's make today
MY舞☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
MY Dance☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
今日にしよう
the absolute best!
MY舞☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
MY Dance☆TONIGHT (DANCING TONIGHT)
せーの！
Ready, set...
ハッピーニューイヤー！
Happy New Year!
おにおに こんこん こんばんはー
Oni-oni, kon-kon, good evening!
夢を叫んだ
I shouted my dream,
「君じゃ無理」
"'You can't do it,'"
立ち尽くんだ暗闇で
Standing frozen in the darkness,
怖かった 怖かった
I was scared, so scared.
照らしてくれたのは
What lit up my way...
カラー
color,
みんなの光
everyone's light.
スター
Star,
これが僕の光
this is my light.
ホロプラス！
HoloPlus!
ライブ最高でしたー！
The live concert was amazing!
感想をホロプラスに投稿っと...
Time to post my thoughts on HoloPlus...
あ！明けましておめでとうございます！
Ah! Happy New Year!
ホロプラス宣伝隊長の春先のどかです！
I'm Harusaki Nodoka, the HoloPlus PR Team Leader!
公式アプリ「ホロプラス」ではカウントダウンライブ連動キャンペーンを開催中！
On the official app "HoloPlus", we're holding a Countdown Live tie-in campaign!
推し活するだけでプレゼントが当たるチャンス...！？
A chance to win prizes just by supporting your favorite talent...?!
詳しくは「ホロプラス」をチェック！
Check "HoloPlus" for details!
2024年も「ホロプラス」をよろしくお願いいたします！
Please support HoloPlus in 2024 as well!
おつホロプラス～！
Otsu HoloPlus~!
綺麗じゃない 綺麗じゃない でも 嫌いじゃない 嫌いじゃないでしょ
It's not pretty, it's not pretty, but you don't hate it, you don't hate it, right?
まっすぐに 不器用でもいい
It's fine even if it's straightforwardly clumsy.
どうでもいい どうでもいいんだよ
It doesn't matter, it really doesn't matter.
君を想う どんな雨も
Whatever rain thinking of you brings,
水たまり踏みつけて 笑われたっていいんだ
Stomping on puddles, it's fine if I'm laughed at.
溢れかえっていいんだから
Because it's okay for it to overflow.
恐れずに前を向いたら
If you look forward without fear...
こんこんきーつねー！
Kon kon kitsune!
ふわふわ尻尾のご奉仕！あなたの心の一番星、白上フブキです！
Serving you with my fluffy tail! The brightest star in your heart, I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
ハイ、フレンズ！
Hi, friends!
皆さん、速報じゃい！
Everyone, I have breaking news!
来る2024年1月5日に
On the upcoming date of January 5th, 2024...
周防パトラちゃんと3Dコラボ配信が決定しました！イエーイ！
A 3D collab stream with Suou Patra has been confirmed! Yay!
1月5日は白上チャンネルで行いますので、皆さんお楽しみに！
It will be held on the Shirakami Channel on January 5th, so stay tuned!
では最後に、パトラちゃんから一言！
And finally, a few words from Patra-chan!
こんばんわんわん！
Good evening-wan-wan!
周防パトラです！
I'm Suou Patra!
1月5日、ホロライブスタジオに遊びに行っちゃうよ！
On January 5th, I'll be visiting the Hololive studio!
皆さん、よろしくお願いします！
Everyone, please look forward to it!